# **ERFAN PAYA**

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+98-911-531-2456



🔀 hp0098v1@gmail.com



Golestan, Iran



Github



LinkedIn

#### SUMMARY

# I am a self-taught programmer who has been working in the front-end field for more than a year and has done various projects for individuals and teams. Because I love coding and programming, I am learning and improving my skills every day.

## SKILLS

## Languages

Typescript, Javascript

## Frameworks & Libraries

Next.js . React.js . Zustand React-hook-form. Zod React-Query . Drizzle Tailwind . Shaden . Mantine

#### **Tools**

Git . Github . Figma . Docker

# **EDUCATION**

# **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING**

MahmooadAbad (Mazndaran) University

2021-Peresent

#### EXPERIENCE

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2024/09 - 2024/10

TATC (Toronto Addication treatment Centres)

- · Implementation of the icl project
- Attendance at work meetings to advance project goals
- Provide better and modern solutions to advance project goals
- Deployment of the project in the host

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2024/06 - 2024/08

Orbyx Team

- · Development of kalinlash and hakar platforms
- Improvement of soft skills
- Attendance at daily meetings and project reviews
- Provide better and modern solutions to advance goals

## **PROJECTS**

# Kalin Lash (E-commerce) 🤌

2024/07 - 2024/09

A full-featured e-commerce platform built with React.js and TypeScript

# Hakar (Entrepreneurship services) 🤌

2024/06 - 2024/07

A platform for finding entrepreneurship services built with React.js and TypeScript

# ICL (analyzing chats of depressed people)

2024/09 - 2024/11

A website for analyzing chats of depressed people built with Next.js and Typescript